[
	{
		"unit": "Unit 1: Primitive Types",
		"type": 2,
		"question": "Write a line that creates a variable named 'hello' and assign it the value 'world' in Java. Write the solution in the shortest way possible (with spaces).",
		"answer": "String hello = \"world\";"
	},
	{
		"unit": "Unit 1: Primitive Types",
		"type": 1,
		"question": "Which of these methods displays an input to the the computer monitor?",
		"options": [
			"System.in.print()",
			"print()",
			"System.out.print()",
			"System.out.input()"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"unit": "Unit 2: Using Objects",
		"type": 1,
		"question": "Which of these are NOT a way to create the string 'test'?",
		"options": [
			"String test = \"hello\";",
			"String test: \"hello\"",
			"String test; test = \"hello\"",
			"String test = new String(\"hello\");"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"unit": "Unit 2: Using Objects",
		"type": 1,
		"question": "What are reference data types also known as?",
		"options": [
			"class data types",
			"java data",
			"variables",
			"constants"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"unit": "Unit 3: Boolean Expressions and If Statements",
		"type": 1,
		"question": "Which of these are NOT a relational operator?",
		"options": [
			"==",
			">",
			"<",
			"=<"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"unit": "Unit 3: Boolean Expressions and If Statements",
		"type": 3,
		"question": "You are given a variable \"day\" that is an integer from 1-7 that represents what day of week it is, from Sunday (1) to Saturday (7). Print out \"true\" or \"false\" whether or not the day is Friday.",
		"input": 6,
		"answer": "true"
	},
	{
		"unit": "Unit 4: Iteration",
		"type": 1,
		"question": "In loops, when does the statement inside the loop execute?",
		"options": [
			"when i = 30",
			"when the condition being checked is false",
			"whenever i = 0",
			"when the condition being checked is true"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"unit": "Unit 4: Iteration",
		"type": 3,
		"question": "You are given an array of strings, \"days\", that represents the days in the week. Loop this array and print every item in one line without any spaces (NOT ln).",
		"input": ["Sunday", "Monday", "Tuesday", "Wednesday", "Thursday", "Friday", "Saturday"],
		"answer": "SundayMondayTuesdayWednesdayThursdayFridaySaturday"
	},
	{
		"unit": "Unit 5: Classes",
		"type": 1,
		"question": "What is the main method's header?",
		"options": [
			"public static main (String[] args)",
			"public void main (String args)",
			"public static void main (String[] args)",
			"private static void main (String args)"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"unit": "Unit 5: Classes",
		"type": 1,
		"question": "What type of method is a print statement?",
		"options": [
			"It is a private method",
			"It is a static method",
			"It is an instance method",
			"It is a non-static method"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"unit": "Unit 6: Array",
		"type": 1,
		"question": "What is a for-each loop used for?",
		"options": [
			"To loop until a condition is true",
			"To loop each variable created in a file",
			"To loop until a condition is false",
			"To loop through all items in an array"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"unit": "Unit 6: Array",
		"type": 2,
		"question": "Declare a string array \"fruits\" with items \"mango\", \"pineapple\", and \"raspberry\". Write the solution in the shortest way possible (with spaces).",
		"answer": "String[] fruits = {\"mango\", \"pineapple\", \"raspberry\"};"
	},
	{
		"unit": "Unit 7: ArrayList",
		"type": 1,
		"question": "What is an ArrayList?",
		"options": [
			"A flexible array object that can change size.",
			"A static array that cannot change.",
			"A dynamic array that can have items with different datatypes.",
			"The same thing as an Array."
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"unit": "Unit 7: ArrayList",
		"type": 2,
		"question": "You are given a lisy called \"myData\". Write the expression that would return the size/length of the list, in the shortest way possible.",
		"answer": "myData.size()"
	},
	{
		"unit": "Unit 8: 2D Array",
		"type": 1,
		"question": "How do you declare a 2D Array of integers?",
		"options": [
			"ArrayList(int[]) numbers = new Type(int)[10][10];",
			"int[][] numbers = new int[10][10];",
			"int[[]] numbers = new int[10[10]];",
			"int[][] numbers = new Type(int)[10][10];"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"unit": "Unit 8: 2D Array",
		"type": 1,
		"question": "Which of these expressions get the number of columns in a 2D array?",
		"options": [
			"numbers[4].length",
			"length(numbers)",
			"numbers.length",
			"length(numbers[4])"
		],
		"answer": 0
	}
]